Finding aid for the Jerry Lewis papers LSC.2124
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Legislative Files, 1969-2013
  - Subseries 3.2: US Congress, California Subject Files, 1979-2013
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Fort Irwin Expansion, 1991, 1992, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Fort Irwin Expansion, 1996-2002 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Fort Irwin Expansion, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Fort Irwin Expansion, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Fort Irwin Expansion, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Fort Irwin Expansion, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Fort Irwin Wilderness Study Area, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Fort Irwin Wilderness, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Forest Fires, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Grazing, BLM, 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Groundwater Contamination, 1997-1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Highland Bridge, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: HUD, VA, EPA Appropriations Requests FY03, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Inland Valley Development Agency, 2005, 2006, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Interior Appropriations Requests FY00, FY01, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Interior Appropriations Requests FY02, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Interior Appropriations Requests FY03, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Interior Appropriations Requests FY05, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Interior Appropriations Requests FY06, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Interior Appropriations, Forest Service, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Inyo County, Argus Wilderness, Bill Gossett, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Kangaroo Rat Protection, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Kangaroo Rat, San Bernardino, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Lake Arrowhead, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Lower Owens River Plan, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mascaro Land Development, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Metropolitan Water District of Southern California, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Miscellaneous Subjects, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave Desert Recovery Plan, Gerry Hiller, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave National Preserve, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave National Preserve, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave National Preserve, 1999-2003 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave National Preserve, 1999-2003 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave National Preserve, 2000-2002 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave National Preserve, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave National Preserve, Cliff McDonald, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave National Preserve, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave National Preserve Amendment, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave National Preserve, Hunting Position, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave Water Bill, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Mojave Water Agency FY07, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Morongo Valley Conservation, 2000, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Morongo Valley Water, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Murietta Creek Flood Control, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Needles, Bureau Bay Project, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Newmark Water Pollution Cleanup, 1996-2000 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Newmark Water Pollution Cleanup, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Norton Air Force Base Reuse, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Norton Air Force Base Reuse, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Norton Air Force Base Reuse, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Nuclear Waste Disposal, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Redlands Habitat Project, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Redlands Habitat Project, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Route 66 Corridor, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea Reclamation Act, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea Reclamation Act, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea Reclamation Act, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea Reclamation Act, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea Reclamation Act, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea Reclamation Act, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea Reclamation Act, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea Reclamation Act, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea Reclamation Act, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea, 1998-2000 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Salton Sea, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Arrowhead Tunnel, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Air Tankers, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest Bark Beetle Project, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest Bark Beetle Project, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest Blight Funding, HUD, 1997-2000 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest Blight Funding, HUD (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, FEMA, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Fire Cost, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Fire Evacuation, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Fire Danger, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Fontana Union Water District, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Future Protection, 1999-2003 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest Land Exchange, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest Land Exchange, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Local Impacts, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Healthy Forests, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Press Coverage, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Sustainability, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Sustainability, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Wildfire Protection, 2003, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Wildfire Mitigation, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Wildfire Mitigation, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: San Bernardino National Forest, Wildfire Mitigation, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Santa Ana Wash Conservation Plan, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Santa Ana River Projects, 1999-2001, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Soboba Luiseños, Water District Settlement, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Soboba Luiseños, Water District Settlement, 2006, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Soboba Luiseños, Water District Settlement, 2006, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: South Coast Air Quality Management, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Timbisha Shoshone Homeland Act, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Timbisha Shoshone Homeland Act, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Timbisha Shoshone Homeland Act, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: US Army Environmental Cleanup, 1998-2000 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: US Army Environmental Cleanup, 1998-2000 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: US Army Environmental Cleanup, 1998-2000 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Ward Valley Nuclear Waste Dump, 1995-1997 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Ward Valley Nuclear Waste Dump, 1995-1997 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Water Appropriations, Morongo Valley, Yucca Valley, Twentynine Palms, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Water Projects, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Water and Land Requests FY08, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Water Projects, Mojave, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Water Resources and Development Act, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Water Resources and Development Act Requests, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Water, San Timoteo Creek, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Water, San Jacinto River, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Water, Sumner Peck, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Land, Water, and Energy: Yucaipa Valley Water District, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Lewis Center Charter Schools, 2011-2012 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Lewis Swim Center, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Local Requests FY07, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Loma Linda Appropriations, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Loma Linda Connected Community Program, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Methamphetamine, 1997-1999 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Mojave Cross, UCLA, 2000-2012 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Mojave Cross, UCLA, 2000-2012 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Mojave Cross, UCLA, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Mojave Cross, UCLA, 2010, 2012 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Mount Fuji, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Nixon Library, 2003-2006 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Nixon Library, 2003-2006 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Pat Morris, Operation Phoenix, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Payment in Lieu of Taxes Program, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Polling, 31st District, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Polling, 31st District, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Public Health/Medicine: CA Medical Association, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Public Health/Medicine: Inland Behavioral and Health Services, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Public Health/Medicine: Jordan Neuroscience, 2007-2012 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Public Health/Medicine: Loma Linda University, Afghanistan, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Public Health/Medicine: Loma Linda University, Proton Beam Therapy, DOE, 1990-1994 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Public Health/Medicine: Loma Linda University, Proton Beam Therapy, DOE, 1990-1994 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Public Health/Medicine: Loma Linda University, Proton Beam Therapy, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Public Health/Medicine: Loma Linda University, Proton Beam Therapy, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Public Health/Medicine: Loma Linda University, Proton Beam Therapy, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Public Health/Medicine: Needles Hospital, 2007-2009 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Public Health/Medicine: St. Bernardine Medical Center, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Public Health/Medicine: Victor Valley Community Hospital, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Public Health/Medicine: West Nile Virus, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Ramsey Street Realignment, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Randy Cunningham, 2006-2007 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Reagan Statue, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Redistricting, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Redistricting, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Redistricting, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Redlands, Environmental Systems Research Institute, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Redlands YMCA, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Riverside County Transportation, Flood Control, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - San Bernardino Appropriations FY04, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - San Bernardino, Child Protective Services, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - San Bernardino, Defense Finance Accounting Services, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - San Bernardino, Internet Funding, 1994, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - San Bernardino, HUD, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - San Bernardino, Neighborhood Initiative Program, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - San Bernardino Election, Candidate's Handbook, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - San Bernardino Police, Federal Grant Application, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - San Jacinto, Luiseño Indians, 2009-2011 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - San Manuel Indians, 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - San Manuel Indians, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - September 11, 2001, Local Clippings, 2001-2002 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Silicon Valley, Executive Breakfast, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Soboba Luiseño Indians, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Soboba Luiseño Indians, Diamond Valley Lake, Soboba Casino, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Soboba Luiseño Indians, Reservation Expansion, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Soboba Luiseño Indians, TANF Grants, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Sonny Bono, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - State Criminal Alien Assistance Program (SCAAP), 1999-2002 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - State Criminal Alien Assistance Program (SCAAP), 1999-2001 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Timbisha Shoshone, Death Valley Restoration Project, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Timbisha Shoshone, Hesperia Casino, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Town Hall Meeting, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Transportation: Appropriations FY99, FY00, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Transportation: Appropriations FY05, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Transportation: Appropriations FY07, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Transportation: Appropriations FY08-FY10, 2007-2009 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Transportation: Appropriations FY08-FY10, 2009, 2012 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Transportation: Appropriations FY12, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Transportation: Appropriations Requests FY00, FY01, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Transportation: Appropriations Requests FY02, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Transportation: Appropriations Requests FY04, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Transportation: Appropriations Requests FY04, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Transportation: Appropriations Requests FY05, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Transportation: Appropriations Requests FY06, 2005-2006 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Transportation: Appropriations Requests FY11, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Transportation: FAA, Aviation, 2005-2009 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Transportation: Helendale Road, 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Transportation: Helendale Road, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Transportation: High Desert Corridor, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Transportation: HUD, Transportation FY08, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Transportation: Inland Empire Goods Movement Gateway, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Transportation: Lake Arrowhead Airport, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Transportation: Lake Arrowhead Airport, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Transportation: Local Transportation Projects, 2006-2011 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Transportation: Local Transportation Plans, 2008-2011 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Transportation: Los Angeles Light Rail, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Transportation: Maglev Alliance, 2000-2002 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Transportation: Ontario International Airport, 2011-2012 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Transportation: Redlands Passenger Rail, 2005-2011 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Transportation: Redlands Passenger Rail, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Transportation: Rialto Airport, 2002-2005 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Transportation: Rialto Airport, 2002-2005 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Transportation: Riverside County Transportation Commission, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Transportation: Tippecanoe I-10 Exchange, 2006-2010 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Transportation: Transportation Equity Act, LU Requests, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Transportation: Transportation Equity Act, LU Requests, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Transportation: Transportation Equity Act, LU Requests, Project List, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Transportation: Transportation Equity Act, LU Requests, High Priority Projects, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - University Research: Loma Linda, National Medical Technology Testbed, 1992, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - University Research: Loma Linda, Proton Beam Therapy, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - University Research: San Bernardino, Arrowhead Regional Medical Center, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - University Research: San Bernardino Community College, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - University Research: San Gorgonio Memorial Hospital, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - University Research: UCLA, US Navy, University Affiliated Research Center, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - University Research: UCLA Resolutions, 2003, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - University Research: University of Redlands, Federal Grants, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - University Research: University of Redlands, Science Funding, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - University Research: Universities, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - University Research: Web Wise Kids Program, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - University Research: Yucaipa Valley Regional Soccer Complex, 2000-2005 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - University Research: Yucca Valley, Green Path North Project, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 3.3. US Congress, National Subject Files, 1979-2013
    This subseries contains files on topics that are primarily of national and international significance, even though some of them may also have some particular relevance to residents of California. The specific types of documents preserved include such things as newspaper clippings, publications, government reports, bill texts, and correspondence. A great deal of the material comes from Lewis's work on the House Committee on Appropriations, although little of it is explicitly labeled as such. The largest subjects covered are "Congress," "Defense," "Foreign Aid/Operations," "Labor," and "Public Health."
    - Agriculture: Appropriations FY99, 1998-1999 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Agriculture: Appropriations FY99, 1998-1999 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Agriculture: Ethanol Tax Incentives, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Agriculture: Farm Bill, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Census FY13, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Clinton Impeachment, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Commerce, Justice, State, Judiciary Subcommittee: Appropriations FY96, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Commerce, Justice, State, Judiciary Subcommittee: Appropriations FY98, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Commerce, Justice, State, Judiciary Subcommittee: Appropriations FY98, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Commerce, Justice, Science Subcommittee: Appropriations FY10, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Commerce, Justice, Science Subcommittee: Appropriations FY12, Full Committee Markup, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Commerce, Justice, Science Subcommittee: Appropriations FY13, Full Committee Markup, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Commerce, Justice, Science Subcommittee: Judicial Pay, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Commerce, Justice, Science Subcommittee: Prisoner Reentry Hearing, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Congress: Appropriations Accomplishments, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Congress: Appropriations, CAO Hearing FY01, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Congress: Appropriations, Chair Pitch, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Congress: Appropriations, Miscellaneous, 2007-2009 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Congress: Appropriations, FY06 Report, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Congress: Appropriations, Steering Committee, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Congress: Committee on Committees, 100th Congress, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Congress: Committee on Committees, 100th Congress, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Congress: Committee on Committees, 100th Congress, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Congress: Committee on Committees, 100th Congress, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Congress: Congressional Art Contest, 2008, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Congress: Congressional Background Publications, 1977-1981, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Congress: Congressional Cemetery, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Congress: Congressional Misconduct, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Congress: Congressional Republican Philosophy, 1989-1994 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Congress: Congressional Reform, 1988-1991 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Congress: Earmark Reform, 2000-2008 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Congress: Earmark Reform, 2000-2008 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Congress: Economic Growth and Opportunity Binder, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Congress: House Republican Conference, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Congress: House Republican Conference, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Congress: House Republican Conference, 1988-1992 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Congress: House Speaker Histories, 1987-1992 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Congress: House Republican Research Committee Sample Publications, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Congress: House Republican Research Committee Sample Publications, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Congress: House Republican Research Committee Sample Publications, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Congress: Legislative Appropriations, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Congress: Legislative Branch FY07, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Congress: Legislative Branch FY07, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Congress: Legislative Branch FY08, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Congress: Legislative Branch FY08, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Congress: Legislative Branch FY13, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Congress: Legislative Digest, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Congress: Legislative Digest, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Congress: Lewis Chairmanship, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Congress: Lewis Investigation, CREW, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Congress: Lewis Investigation, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Congress: Library of Congress FY02, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Congress: Member Retreat, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Congress: Program for Newly Elected Members of Congress, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Congress: Program for Newly Elected Members of Congress, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Congress: Program for Newly Elected Members of Congress, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Congress: Republican Research Committee, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Congress: Republican Retreat 2008, Earmark Reform (Box 36, Folder 19)